A Guide to the Evert B. Clark Papers, 1949-1988
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Newsweek clippings 1975-1978 (Box-folder 11-20-23)
- Clark files to Newsweek #1-#7 1968-1971 (Box-folder 11-24-35)
- Clark files to Newsweek #8-#17 1971-1976 (Box-folder 12-1-25)
- Clark files to Newsweek #18-#19 1976-1977 (Box-folder 13-1-6)
- Business Week clippings 1978-1988 (Box-folder 13-7-10)
- Miscellaneous clippings 1964-1988 (Box-folder 13-11)
- Astronautics & Aeronautics clippings and drafts 1966-1969 (Box-folder 13-12)
- Space/Aeronautics clippings 1968-1969 (Box-folder 13-13)
- "The Airport Mess" (Saturday Review) 1968-1969 (Box-folder 13-14)
- Miscellaneous news clippings 1971-1972 (Box-folder 13-15)
- Public Information Center - miscellaneous clippings 1977-1978 (Box-folder 13-16)
- The Washington Post Glomar Explorer clipping 1978 (Box-folder 13-17)
- Bouillion, Joseph 1967-1976 (Box-folder 13-18)
- Notes - book, drugs 1968-1972 (Box-folder 13-19)
- Hearings before House Committee on Crime - heroin 1970 (Box-folder 13-20)
- Panama 1970-1971 (Box-folder 13-21)
- Contrabandista notebooks 1-15 1970-1972 (Box-folder 13-22-25)
- Drug smuggling ca.1971 (Box-folder 13-26)
- Richard, Rafael A. 1971 (Box-folder 13-27)
- Ricord, Auguste 1971-72 (Box-folder 13-28)
- Drug smuggling reports, notes 1971-1972 (Box-folder 13-29)
- Paraguay 1971-1972 (Box-folder 13-30)
- Drug war results 1972 (Box-folder 13-31)
- Drug smuggling case histories and information 1972 (Box-folder 13-32)
- Drugs - South America and Central America clippings 1972 (Box-folder 13-33)
- International drug news 1972 (Box-folder 13-34)
- "Efforts to Prevent Heroin from Illicitly Reaching the United States" 1972 (Box-folder 14-1)
- Mafia at War 1972 (Box-folder 14-2)
- Pharmacy security standards 1972 (Box-folder 14-3)
- Drug traffickers 1972 (Box-folder 14-4)
- Ricord, Auguste extradition 1972 (Box-folder 14-5)
- Ricord, Auguste 1972 (Box-folder 14-6)
- Paris "Match" - drug trafficking 1972 (Box-folder 14-7)
- Cocaine 1972 (Box-folder 14-8)
- Drugs - international 1972 (Box-folder 14-9)
- White House remarks on drugs 1972 (Box-folder 14-10)
- McGovern / Shriver - drug smuggling 1972 (Box-folder 14-11)
- Smuggling - clippings 1972-1973 (Box-folder 14-12)
- Department of Justice narcotics statement (regarding 1972) 1973 (Box-folder 14-13)
- Contrabandista gift list 1973 (Box-folder 14-14)
- Drug smuggling - clippings 1974 (Box-folder 14-15)
- Police conspiracy - clippings 1974 (Box-folder 14-16)
- Working drafts n.d. (Box-folder 14-17)
- Contrabandista carbons n.d. (Box-folder 14-18)
- Chapter 1 "The Asuncion Affair" n.d. (Box-folder 14-19)
- Chapter 2 drafts n.d. (Box-folder 14-20)
- Chapter 2 1st, 2nd, 3rd versions n.d. (Box-folder 14-21)
- Chapter 3 pages 14-27 n.d. (Box-folder 14-22)
- Chapter 8 draft n.d. (Box-folder 14-23)
- Contrabandista! summary 1972 (Box-folder 14-24)
- Index and notes 1972 (Box-folder 14-25)
- Praeger contracts 1972-1973 (Box-folder 14-26)
- Contrabandista! contracts, overseas rights, etc. 1972-74 (Box-folder 14-27)
- Contrabandista! correspondence, notes, etc. 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14-28)
- Contrabandista! reviews, promotion 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14-29)
- Book royalties 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14-30)
- Praeger-Gallimard contract 1975-1976 (Box-folder 14-31)
- Book files 1975-1981 (Box-folder 14-32)
- Space Weapons chapter 2 - background to Cosmos 954 nuclear spacecraft re-entry; other underestimations 1968-1978 (Box-folder 14-33)
- Space Weapons chapter 7 - other satellites 1960-1978 (Box-folder 14-34-35)
- Space Weapons chapter 8 - Fractional Orbital Bombardment System (FOBS) 1967-1971 (Box-folder 14-36)
- Space Weapons chapter 9 - Manned Orbiting Laboratory (MOL) 1965-1969 (Box-folder 14-37)
- Space Weapons chapter 10 - bases 1969 (Box-folder 14-38)
- Space Weapons chapter 11 - NORAD monitoring 1967-1977 (Box-folder 14-39-40)
- Space Weapons chapter 14 - Salyut Soviet space capsule 1965-1977 (Box-folder 14-41)
- Space Weapons miscellaneous 1969-1978 (Box-folder 14-42)
- Life magazine cover with Evert B. Clark in the background 1958 (Box-folder 15-1)
- Apollo 11 memorabilia 1969 (Box-folder 15-2)
- Watergate - IRS 1971-1974 (Box-folder 15-3)